[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":85922,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":120613,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":9951,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":130565,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"4+5=9-6=3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3","4+5=9-6=3"],"rt":29843,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":160409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":11671,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":172081,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4761,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":176842,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2994,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":179837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with t he first  number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":8418,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":188256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2230,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":190487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4284,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":194772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1266,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":196039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3117,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":199156,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1357,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":200514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4251,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":204766,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1755,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":206522,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"W hat is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3148,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":209671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1331,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":211002,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or  bigger,  you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4395,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":215397,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1197,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":216596,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4283,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":220882,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1179,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":222062,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3800,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":225863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1148,"trial_type":"feedba ck","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":227013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":17362,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":244379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<su b>6</sub >). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":63445,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":307827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":12315,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":320144,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3545,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":323690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the  inverse  of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3077,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":326768,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1355,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":328124,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":330948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":987,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":331936,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3310,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":335246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</ sub> 4 =  0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1245,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":336492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2989,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":339482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5640,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":345122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<s ub>6</su b>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":22775,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":367898,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2,  and 0 =  2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":56122,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":424022,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4428,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":428450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":11801,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":440252,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a gen erator u nder +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3808,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":444060,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":19180,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":463241,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4  a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6854,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":470096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1977,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":472073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"N o","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4037,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":476111,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2594,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":478706,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one  practice  question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":22653,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":501361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3828,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":505190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1063,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":506254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3646,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":509901,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":10304,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":520208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4905,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":525115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3547,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":528664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":7091,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":535756,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":10706,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":546463,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4+1=5 its less than 9 so it stays the same","explanation_history":["4+1=5 its less than 9 so it stays the same"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":25435,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":571899,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8+4=12-9=3 12 is more than 8 so i minus 9","explanation_history":["8+4=12-9=3 12 is more than 8 so i mu","8+4=12-9=3 12 is more than 8 so i minus 9"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":39337,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":611237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"-9","explain":true,"explanation":"if a sum is more than 8 you subtract 9 if not then it stays the same","explanation_history":["if a sum is more than 8 you subtrac ","if a sum is more than 8 you subtract 9 if not then it stays the same"],"response_history":["its ","its","it","i","if a sum is more than 8 then you ","-9"],"rt":55871,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":667109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":34322,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":701432,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Wha t is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":11191,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":712624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":4681,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":717306,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"3+6=9 so there for 6 is the inverse because it would = 0 because 9-9=0","explanation_history":["3+6=9 so there for 6 is the inverses","3+6=9 so there for 6 is the inverse because it would = 0 because 9-9=0"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":69255,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":786562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because 2,345678 does not help to =9","explanation_history":["because it does","because it doe","because it do","because it d","because it ","because it","because i","because 2,345678 does not help to =9"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":112865,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":899431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"m ulti","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"yes because 3+3+3=9 and so on","explanation_history":["yes becasue ","yes becasue","yes becasu","yes becas","yes because 3+3+3=9 and so on"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":25928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":925361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"because 5+4=9","explanation_history":["becasue 5+4=9","because 5+4=9"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":22621,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":947983,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"because 6+3=9","explanation_history":["because 6+3=9"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":27482,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":975467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":25661,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1001129,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1-+_n","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1-+_n"],"rt":31295,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1032425,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x++_n","explain":true,"explanation":"because to get the inverse you must add whatever you can to get the x to equal x","explanation_history":["because to get the inverse you must add whater you can to get then","because to get the inverse you must add whater you can to get thex ","because to get the inverse you must add whater you can to get thex","because to get the inverse you must add whater you can to get the x to equal ","because to get the inverse you must add whatevr you can to get the x to equal ","because to get the inverse you must add whatever you can to get the x to equal x"],"response_history":["x-+n","x-+_n","x+_n","x++_n"],"rt":87082,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1119509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"if you can add it to itself a couple times","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["if you can add it to itself a couple times"],"rt":20705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1140217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":12726,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1152946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":4694,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1157641,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":10825,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1168467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"because you want to be able to divided the number into n","explanation_history":["because you want to be able to dived ","because you want to be able to dived","because you want to be able to dive","because you want to be able to divided the number into n"],"response_history":["False"],"rt":48609,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1217076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Alwa ys","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":9399,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1226476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"because its not clear what the number is so its hard to tell","explanation_history":["because its not clear what the number is so its hard to tell"],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":37425,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1263902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x + <sub>n</ sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":27551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1291454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":9425,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1300880,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"28","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["28"],"rt":2902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1303782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 5-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":2877,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1306660,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"my most advanced was college algebra","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["my most advanced was college algebra"],"rt":18081,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1324742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":6042,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1330784,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not  often o r recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":3128,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1333912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3202,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1337114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1340361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3086,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1343448,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2060,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1345508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["english"],"rt":6041,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1351549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":5346,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1356896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"on the last question i hit the space bar before  i typed  anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  thank you","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["the last question i hit the space bar beroe i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why ","the last question i hit the space bar beoe i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why ","the last question i hit the space bar befoe i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why ","the last question i hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why ","the last question i hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","the last question  hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","the last question i hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure  why.  ","the last question if hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","the last question if  hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","the last question if t hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","the last question if the hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","the last question ihit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","the last question i hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","othe last question i hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","onthe last question i hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  ","on the  last question i hit the space bar before i typed anything and it automatically moved me forward. Im not sure why.  thank you"],"rt":76059,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1432956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]